A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Healthy Steps for Young Children Program, SG 2, Series 6 FA498
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1991-2006; 4
  - City University - Michael Barth - ICF, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 588)
  - ICF - Consultants - Chonological File, 2004 June (Box 107, Folder 589)
  - ICF - Consultants - Chonological File, 2004 July-November (Box 107, Folder 590)
  - ICF - Consultants - Chonological File, 2004 December-2005 March (Box 108, Folder 591)
  - ICF - Consultants - Chonological File, 2005 April-2006 April (Box 108, Folder 592)
  - ICF - Consultants - Chonological File, 2006 April-August (Box 108, Folder 593)
  - ICF - Kaiser Monitoring Call Reports, 1997-1999 (Box 108, Folder 594)
  - ICF - Retreat Meeting, 1995 December 28-29 (Box 108, Folder 595)
  - ICF - 95-81 - Administration & Budget, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 596)
  - ICF - 95-81 - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 597)
  - ICF - 95-81 - Faxes, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 598-600)
  - ICF - 95-81 - Grant Products, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 601-602)
  - ICF - 95-81 - Meeting Materials, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 603-605)
  - ICF - 96180 - Administration, 1995-1997 (Box 110, Folder 606-607)
  - ICF - 96180 - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 608-609)
  - ICF - 96180 - Disney Letters, 1996-1997 (Box 111, Folder 610)
  - ICF - 96180 - Faxes, 1996 (Box 111, Folder 611-615)
  - ICF - 96180 - Funding Needs, 1996 (Box 111, Folder 616)
  - ICF - 96180 - Grant Products, 1995-1996 (Box 112, Folder 618-621)
  - ICF - 96180 - Helping Children Take Healthy Steps - Abstracts of Selected Articles on Early Childhood Intervention, 1997 Feb. (Box 112, Folder 622)
  - ICF - 96180 - Internet/Web Site Options, 1995-1997 (Box 112, Folder 623)
  - ICF - 96180 - Management Meeting Minutes - To Do Lists, 1995-1996 (Box 112, Folder 624)
  - ICF - 96180 - Meeting Materials, 1996 (Box 113, Folder 625-626)
  - ICF - 96180 - Protocols, 1996 (Box 113, Folder 627)
  - ICF - 96180 - Site Updates and Issues, 1996 September-October (Box 113, Folder 628)
  - ICF - 96957 - Affiliate Sites - Administration, 1996-1998 (Box 113, Folder 629)
  - ICF - 96957 - Affiliate Sites - Board, 1996 July (Box 113, Folder 630)
  - ICF - 96957 - Affiliate Sites, 1996-1997 (Box 113, Folder 631)
  - ICF - 96957 - Affiliate Sites - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 113, Folder 632-633)
  - ICF - 96957 - Affiliate Sites - Chicago Sites, 1996-1997 (Box 113, Folder 634)
  - ICF - 96957 - Faxes, 1997 (Box 113, Folder 635)
  - ICF - 96957 - Grant Products, 1997 (Box 113, Folder 636, Box 114, Folder 637)
  - ICF - 96957 - Kaiser, 1995-1997 (Box 114, Folder 638)
  - ICF - 96957 - Overall Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 114, Folder 639)
  - ICF/Barth - 990122 - Grant Products, 1998 October-2000 (Box 119, Folder 683-685, Box 120, Folder 686)
  - ICF/Barth - 990122 - Partnership Paper, 1998-1999 (Box 120, Folder 687)
  - ICF - 970269 - Administration & Budget, 1994, 1996-1998 (Box 114, Folder 640)
  - ICF - 970269 - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 641)
  - ICF - 970269 - Faxes, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 642-643)
  - ICF - 970269 - Grant Products, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 644-645)
  - ICF - 970269 - Management Meeting, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 646)
  - ICF - 970269 - Monitoring Visits - Fort Bend Richmond, TX, 1997 July 21 (Box 115, Folder 647)
  - ICF - 970269 - Partnership Paper, 1997 September (Box 115, Folder 648)
  - ICF - 970269 - Proposal, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 649)
  - ICF - 970271 - Authorization for Sites - Boston, MA, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 650)
  - ICF - 970271 - Authorization for Sites - Detroit, MI, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 651)
  - ICF - 970271 - Authorization for Sites - Kansas City, MO, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 652)
  - ICF - 970271 - Authorization for Sites - New York, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 653)
  - ICF - 970271 - Authorization for Sites - Pittsburgh, PA, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 654)
  - ICF - 970271 - Authorization for Sites - Amarillo, TX, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 655)
  - ICF - Kaiser Grant - 970579 - Healthy Steps Video, 1996-1997 (Box 115, Folder 656)
  - ICF - Revisions to Healthy Steps Video - 971067, 1997-1999 (Box 116, Folder 657)
  - ICF - 980200 - Program Direction and Operation - Administration, 1997-1998 (Box 116, Folder 658)
  - ICF - 980200 - Program Direction and Operation - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 116, Folder 659-661)
  - ICF - 980200 - Program Direction and Operation - Expense Report, 1998 (Box 116, Folder 662)
  - ICF - 980200 - Program Direction and Operation - Faxes, 1998 (Box 116, Folder 663-665)
  - ICF - 980200 - Program Direction and Operation - Grant, 1997-1998 (Box 117, Folder 666)
  - ICF - 980200 - Program Direction and Operation - Grant Products, 1998 (Box 117, Folder 667-671)
  - ICF - 980200 - Program Direction and Operation - Management Meeting, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 672-674)
  - ICF - 980200 - Program Direction and Operation - Proposal, LOA, P & R, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 675)
  - ICF - 980200 - Program Direction and Operation - Report, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 676-677)
  - ICF - 980200 - Program Direction and Operation - Subcontract - Healthy Steps Stories - Randi L. Gould Project, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 678)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Administration, 1998-1999 (Box 122, Folder 703)
  - ICF/Barth - 990122 - Proposal, LOA, P&R, 1997-1999 (Box 120, Folder 688-689)
  - ICF - 2000199 - Administrative, LOA, P & R, 1999-2001 (Box 120, Folder 690)
  - ICF - 2000199 - Bob Young Award, 2000 May 4, June 30 (Box 120, Folder 691)
  - ICF - 2000199 - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 120, Folder 692)
  - ICF - 2000199 - Grant Products, 2000-2001 (Box 120, Folder 693, Box 121, Folder 694-698)
  - ICF - 2000199 - Proposal, 1999 (Box 122, Folder 699)
  - ICF - 2000199 - Second Year Healthy Steps Expenditures by Sites (Box 122, Folder 700)
  - ICF - Final Report - Healthy Steps for Young Children Program - Support for Program Direction and Operations - Contract # 20020695 - Michael Barth - ICF Consulting, 2003 July 31 (Box 122, Folder 702)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Boston University, 1994-1996, 1998 (Box 122, Folder 704)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 122, Folder 705-706)
  - ICF - 2000199 - Work and Cost Model, 1999 (Box 122, Folder 701)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Grant Products, 1998-1999 (Box 122, Folder 707, Box 123, Folder 708-712, Box 124, Folder 713)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Copyright, 1994-1999 (Box 124, Folder 714)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Multimedia Policy Makers - Level Survey - Raw Data & Group Meeting, 1998 Oct. 14, Dec. 2 (Box 124, Folder 715)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Multimedia Project - Assessment Vol. I & II, 1999 Sept. (Box 124, Folder 716)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Multimedia Project - Audience Teasting, 1998 (Box 124, Folder 717)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Multimedia Project - Fundraising, 1998-1999 (Box 124, Folder 718)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Multimedia Project - MMK Distribution/ Marketing, 2000-2001 (Box 124, Folder 719)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Multimedia Project - MMK Income & Expense Report, 2001 July 30 (Box 124, Folder 720)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Multimedia Project - Proposal, LOA, Budget, 1998 (Box 124, Folder 721)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Multimedia Project - Years III & IV, 1998-1999 (Box 124, Folder 722)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Multimedia Project - Retreat, 1998 May 18 (Box 124, Folder 723)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Multimedia Training Package - Lisa Zbar - Subcontract Toby Levine, 1997-1998 (Box 124, Folder 724)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Multimedia Training Package - Proposal, 1998 January 14 (Box 125, Folder 725)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Multimedia Training Package - Video Toby Levine Communication, Inc., 1998 April - May (Box 125, Folder 726)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Multimedia Training & Resource Kit - Royalty Agreement with Boston University, 1996-1999 (Box 125, Folder 727)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 980486 - Healthy Steps Multimedia - Technical Assistance - Meeting, 1998 Nov. 9 (Box 125, Folder 728)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 99047 - Training Package for a Child Development Approach in Pediatic Practives, Phase Three, 1999 November (Box 125, Folder 729)
  - Independent Production Fund, Inc. - 99047 - Training and Resource Kit - Conference Call - MB, L. Zbar, M. Sanoff, J. Mettner, and T. Levine, 2001 November 14, 19 (Box 125, Folder 730)
  - Jobs for the Future - 96007 - Administration & Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 125, Folder 731)
  - Jobs for the Future - 96007 - Background Material, 1995-1996 (Box 125, Folder 732)
  - Jobs for the Future - 96007 - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 125, Folder 733)
  - Jobs for the Future - 96007 - Findings from the Survey of Youth Mentoring and Career - Related Activities in Hospitals, 1997 May-July (Box 125, Folder 734)
  - Jobs for the Future - 96007 - Grant Products, 1996-1997 (Box 125, Folder 735)
  - Jobs for the Future - 96007 - Grant Products, 1997-1998 (Box 126, Folder 736)
  - Jobs for the Future - Promoting STC & Mentoring in the Healthcare System - Administration, 1996-1997 (Box 126, Folder 737)
  - Jobs for the Future - Promoting STC & Mentoring in the Healthcare System - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 126, Folder 738)
  - Jobs for the Future - Promoting STC & Mentoring in the Healthcare System - Grant Products, 1997 (Box 126, Folder 739)
  - Jobs for the Future - 96007 - Proposal, 1995-1996 (Box 126, Folder 740)
  - Jobs for the Future - School-to-Work ToolKit, 1994 (Box 127)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital Youth Mentoring Program - Background, Grant, Profiles, and Final Report, 1995 (Box 128, Folder 741)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital Youth Mentoring Program - Main Medical Center Site Visit - Shawn La France, 1994 December (Box 128, Folder 742)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital Youth Mentoring Program - Meeting, 1995 February 9-10 (Box 128, Folder 743)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital Youth Mentoring Program - Meeting, 1995 July 25-26 (Box 128, Folder 744)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital Youth Mentoring Program - Network Meeting - KTY Trips, 1996, 1997 Feb. 6-8 (Box 128, Folder 745)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital Youth Mentoring Program - Summary, 1993-1996 (Box 128, Folder 746)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 96005 - Administration & Budget, 1995-1997 (Box 128, Folder 747)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 96005 - Background & Materials, 1996 (Box 128, Folder 748)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 96005 - Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 129, Folder 749)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 96005 - Grant Products, 1995-1997 (Box 129, Folder 750-751)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 96145 - Administration, 1995-1997 (Box 129, Folder 752-753)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 96145 - Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 129, Folder 754-755)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 961455 - Evaluation Design, 1996 (Box 129, Folder 756-757)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 96145 - Evaluation - Forms, 1996 (Box 130, Folder 758)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 96145 - Final Evaluation Instrument - Part 2, 1996 (Box 130, Folder 759)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 96145 - Formative Evaluation, 1996-1997 (Box 130, Folder 760)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 96145 - Evaluation - Manual Forms, 1996 June 25 (Box 130, Folder 761)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 96145 - Grant Products, 1996-1997 (Box 130, Folder 762-765)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 96145 - Healthcare Industry Symposium, 1996 March (Box 130, Folder 766)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 96145 - Products, 1996 (Box 131, Folder 767)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene & Public Health - 96005 - Proposal, 1995 September 8 (Box 131, Folder 768)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - 96844 - Administration, 1996-1998 (Box 131, Folder 769)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - 96844 - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 131, Folder 770)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - 96844 - Grant Products, 1996-1997 (Box 131, Folder 771)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - 96844 - Proposal - Board, 1996 July (Box 131, Folder 772)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - 999027 - Business Plan, 1999 (Box 131, Folder 773)
  - Johns Hopkins University - 970270 - Administration, 1996-1998 (Box 131, Folder 774)
  - Johns Hopkins University - 970270 - Administration & Budget, 1996-1999 (Box 131, Folder 775)
  - Johns Hopkins University - 970270 - Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 131, Folder 776)
  - Johns Hopkins University - 970270 - Collaborative Research Agreement, 1997 July (Box 132, Folder 777)
  - Johns Hopkins University - 970270 - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 132, Folder 778)
  - Johns Hopkins University - 970270 - Grant Products, 1997-1998 (Box 132, Folder 779-782)
  - Johns Hopkins University - 970270 - Grant Proposal, 1996 (Box 132, Folder 783)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Phase III - Evaluation, 1996-1998 (Box 133, Folder 784)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Phase III - Evaluation - Administration, 1995-1997 (Box 133, Folder 785)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Phase III - Evaluation - Analysis, 1997-1998 (Box 133, Folder 786)
  - Johns Hopkins University - W.T. Grant Proposal, 1996-1998 (Box 133, Folder 787-789)
  - John Hopkins University - Phase III - 971021 - Identifying Projects Re: Children and Violence - L. Wissow, 1997-1998 (Box 133, Folder 790)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Phase III - Year One - Final Report - National Evaluation, 1998 Feb. 6 (Box 134, Folder 791)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Phase III - Year 2 - Final Report - National Evaluation Vol. 1 of 2, 1999 Feb. 12 (Box 134, Folder 792)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Phase III - Year 2 - Final Report - National Evaluation Vol. 2 of 2, 1999 Feb. 12 (Box 134, Folder 793)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Phase III - Year 2 - Final Report - National Evaluation Vol. 2, No. 2, 1999 March 1 (Box 134, Folder 794)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Phase III - Year 3 - Final Report - National Evaluation, 2000 Feb. 15 (Box 134, Folder 795)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Phase III - Year 4 - Final Report - National Evaluation, 2001 Feb. 1, 15 (Box 134, Folder 796)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Phase III - Year 5 - Final Report - National Evaluation, 2002 Febfuary (Box 134, Folder 797)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Healthy Steps Evaluation - 980143 - Baseline Provider Survey - Sustaining Services for Children, 1998 June 1, 4 (Box 134, Folder 798)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Healthy Steps Evaluation - 980143 - Changes to Evaluation - Design & Budget, 1998 (Box 134, Folder 799)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Healthy Steps Evaluation - 980143 - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 134, Folder 800)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Healthy Steps Evaluation - 980143 - Presentation Material, 1997-1998 (Box 134, Folder 801)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Healthy Steps Evaluation - 980143 - Proposed Changes to Evaluation, 1997-1998 (Box 134, Folder 802)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Healthy Steps Evaluation - 980143 - Proposal for Research Collaboration, 1998 (Box 135, Folder 803)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Healthy Steps Evaluation - 980143 - Proposal, LOA, P & R, 1997-1999 (Box 135, Folder 804)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Healthy Steps Evaluation - 980143 - Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 135, Folder 805)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Healthy Steps Evaluation - 980143 - Report/Grant Products, 1997-1998 (Box 135, Folder 806)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Healthy Steps Evaluation - 980143 - Year Six Budget, 1998 (Box 135, Folder 807)
    - Johns Hopkins University - National Evaluation Working Papers Series - A Profile of Healthy Steps - Meeting the Needs of Very Young Children Vol. 1, No. 2, 1998 March 15 (Box 135, Folder 808)
  - Johns Hopkins University - National Evaluation Working Papers Series - Baseline Key Informant Interviews - A Summary Report Vol. 1, No. 3, 1998 April 1 (Box 135, Folder 809)
  - Johns Hopkins University - National Evaluation Working Papers Series - Methods for Determining Healthy Steps Costs for the Cost-Effectiveness Analysis Vol. 1, No. 5, 1999 Jan. 31 (Box 135, Folder 810)
  - Johns Hopkins University - National Evaluation Working Papers Series - Assessing the Impact of Pediatric-Based Developmental Services on Infants, Families and Clinicians: Challenges to Evaluating the Healthy Steps Program Vol, 1, No. 1, 1999 Feb. 1 (Box 135, Folder 811)
  - Johns Hopkins University - National Evaluation Working Papers Series - Healthy Steps Families Baseline - A Summary of Newborn Form Data Vol. 1, No. 6, 1999 April 30 (Box 135, Folder 812)
  - Johns Hopkins University - National Evaluation Working Papers Series - Year One Cost Analysis Vol. 1, No. 8, 1999 Nov. 15 (Box 135, Folder 813)
  - Johns Hopkins University - National Evaluation Working Papers Series - Healthy Steps Program Services in the First Year of Life: A Summary of Healthy Steps Specialists' Contacts with Families Vol. 2, No. 2, 2000 Feb. 10 (Box 135, Folder 814)
  - Johns Hopkins University - National Evaluation Working Papers Series - Healthy Steps Families at 6 Months - A Summary of 6 - Month Parent Questionnaire Data Vol. 1, No. 9, 2000 April 21 (Box 136, Folder 815)
  - Johns Hopkins University - National Evaluation Working Papers Series - Implementing Healthy Steps - Report from the Process Evaluation Vol. 2, No. 7, 2001 Dec. 15 (Box 136, Folder 816)
  - Johns Hopkins University - National Evaluation Working Papers Series - Sustainability, Institutionalization and Related Concepts in the Context of Healthy Steps, Vol. 2, No. 4, 2001 December 15 (Box 136, Folder 817)
  - Johns Hopkins University - National Evaluation Working Papers Series - Year Three Cost Analysis, Vol. 2, No. 6, 2001 December 21 (Box 136, Folder 818)
  - Johns Hopkins University - 99096 - Administration & Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 136, Folder 819)
  - Johns Hopkins University - 99096 - Conference Applications, 1999 July 15 (Box 136, Folder 821)
  - Johns Hopkins University - 99096 - Phase III, Year 3 - Grant Products, 1998-2000 (Box 136, Folder 822-824, Box 137, Folder 825-829)
  - Johns Hopkins University - 99096 - Phase III Quarterly Program Report and Grant Products, 1999 (Box 137, Folder 829)
  - Johns Hopkins University - 99096 - Proposal, 1998-1999, 1998 March-September (Box 138, Folder 830)
  - Johns Hopkins University - 99096 - Proposal, LOA, P & R, 1997-1999 (Box 138, Folder 831)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation - 94-25 - Administration, 1993-1995 (Box 138, Folder 832)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation - 94-25 - Administration, 1995-1996 (Box 138, Folder 833)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation - 94-25 - Administration & Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 138, Folder 834)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation - 94-25 - Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 138, Folder 835)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation - 94-25 - Grant Products, 1993-1995 (Box 138, Folder 836-837, Box 139, Folder 838)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation - 94-25 - Readings, 1993 (Box 139, Folder 839)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation - 95590 - Administration, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 840)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation - 95590 - Grant Products, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 841)
  - Mc Manus Health Policy, Inc. - 980554 - Grant Products, 1998-1999 (Box 139, Folder 842-843)
  - Mc Manus Health Policy, Inc.- 980554 - Improving the Use of Medicaid to Promote Healthy Child Development, 1997 (Box 139, Folder 844)
  - Mc Manus Health Policy, Inc.- 980554 - Improving Medicaid Financing, 1997-1998 (Box 139, Folder 845)
  - Mc Manus Health Policy, Inc. - 980554 - Pediatric Development Services Program- Correspondence, 1998 (Box 140, Folder 846)
  - Mc Manus Health Policy, Inc. - 980554 - Pediatric Development Services Program -Proposal, LOA, & Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 140, Folder 847)
  - Mc Manus Health Policy, Inc. - 95456 - Administration and Budget, 1995 (Box 140, Folder 848)
  - Mc Manus Health Policy, Inc. - 95456 - Background Materials, 1995 (Box 140, Folder 849)
  - Mc Manus Health Policy, Inc. - 95456 - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 140, Folder 850)
  - Mc Manus Health Policy, Inc. - 95456 - Grant Products, 1995 (Box 140, Folder 851-852)
  - Medicaid Managed Care Project - Articles, 1998 (Box 140, Folder 853)
  - Medicaid Managed Care Project - Background Materials on Medicaid - MKA's, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 854)
  - Medicaid Managed Care Project - Health Services Management and Policy - Sara Rosenbaum, 1998 (Box 140, Folder 855)
  - Medicaid Managed Care Project - Materials from MKA, 1997 (Box 140, Folder 856)
  - Medicaid Managed Care Project - Pediatric Development Services - Conference Call, 1998 June 10 (Box 140, Folder 857)
  - Medicaid Managed Care Project - Pediatric Development Services - Management Meetings, 1998 April-October (Box 141, Folder 858-859)
  - Medicaid Managed Care Project - Pediatric Development Services - Peter Budetti, Progress Report, 1998 Aug. (Box 141, Folder 860)
  - Medicaid Managed Care Project - Peggy McManus and Harriette Fox - Summary of Prediatric Development Services Program, 1998 July (Box 141, Folder 861)
  - Medicaid Managed Care Project - Program Plan Meeting, 1999 April (Box 141, Folder 862)
  - Medicaid Policies and Programs Targeted the Healthy Development of Young Children - Board Meeting, 1998 April (Box 141, Folder 863)
  - Proposal Review Meeting - Medicaid, 1998 June (Box 141, Folder 864)
  - Medicaid Program Plan Meeting, 1998 January 13-14 (Box 142, Folder 865)
  - Volume 1 - Negotiating the New Health System: A Nationwide Study of Medicaid Managed Care Contracts, 1997 February (Box 143, Folder 866)
  - Mentoring Makes a Difference - Findings from The Commonwealth Fund 1998 Survey of Adults Mentoring Young People, 1998 July (Box 142, Folder 867)
  - MEM Associates - Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 142, Folder 868-870)
  - MEM Associates - Faxes, 1995 February-July (Box 142, Folder 871)
  - MEM Associates - Faxes, 1995 August-1997 (Box 143, Folder 872-875)
  - MEM Associates - 980203 - Administration, 1997-2000 (Box 143, Folder 876)
  - MEM Associates - 980203 - Building Support, 1997-2000 (Box 144, Folder 877)
  - MEM Associates - 980203 - Contact Binder, 1994-1997 (Box 144, Folder 878-879)
  - MEM Associates - 980203 - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 144, Folder 880-882, Box 145, Folder 883-885)
  - MEM Associates - 980203 - Faxes, 1998-1999 (Box 145, Folder 885)
  - MEM Associates - 980203 - Grant Products, 1999-2000 (Box 145, Folder 886)
  - MEM Associates - 980203 - Paper Materials, 1998 (Box 145, Folder 887)
  - MEM Associates - 980203 - Proposal, LOA, P & R, 1997 (Box 145, Folder 888)
  - MEM Associates - 980203 - Proposal, 1997-1998 (Box 145, Folder 889)
  - MEM Associates - 980203 - Reports, 1997-1999 (Box 145, Folder 890)
  - National Committee to Prevent Child Abuse - 96698, 1995-1997 (Box 146, Folder 891)
  - National Committee to Prevent Child Abuse - 96698, 1997-1998 (Box 146, Folder 892)
  - National League of Cities - 95900, 1995-1996 (Box 146, Folder 893)
  - NYC Health and Hospitals Corporation - Reach Out and Read - 970707, 1997 (Box 146, Folder 894)